Register of the S. I. Hayakawa papers
Hoover Institution Archives
S. I. Hayakawa papers
1926-1994
82111
Hoover Institution Archives
549 manuscript boxes, 35 cubic foot boxes, 40 card file boxes, 17 oversize boxes, 1 motion picture film reel (266.2 linear feet)
Correspondence, speeches and writings, memoranda, reports, government documents, clippings, other printed matter, photographs, sound tape cassettes, videotape cassettes, and memorabilia relating to semantics and education, student radicalism, the Japanese American community, American politics, the Republican Party, and American foreign relations and domestic policy.
Hayakawa, S. I. (Samuel Ichiyé), 1906-1992.
Access
Box 463 is closed; access images are available in Box 462. Remainder of collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1982, with increments received in later years.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
United States senator from California, 1977-1983.
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, speeches and writings, memoranda, reports, government documents, clippings, other printed matter, photographs, sound tape cassettes, videotape cassettes, and memorabilia relating to semantics and education, student radicalism, the Japanese American community, American politics, the Republican Party, and American foreign relations and domestic policy.
California--Politics and government--1951-; United States--Foreign relations--1977-1981.; United States--Foreign relations--1981-1989.; United States--Politics and government--1977-1981.; United States--Politics and government--1981-1989.; United States. Congress. Senate.; Language and languages.; Universities and colleges--United States.; Student movements--United States.; Japanese Americans.; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); Statesmen--United States.
- Washington Office, Administrative/Legislative Files (Boxes 1-265)
  - Administrative memos (Box 1)
  - Advisory Committees
    - Agriculture
    - Energy
    - Health
    - Immigration
    - International trade
    - Natural resources
  - Africa trip, 1982
  - Agriculture
  - Aliens/SSI
  - Archivist/Disposition of SIH papers
  - ASEAN trip, August 1982
  - Big Sur
  - Briefing book
    - August 1979
    - August 1979 (Box 2)
    - July 1980
    - Fall 1980
    - April 1981
  - Briefing cards, 1981
  - Bruinsma for Senate (Box 3)
  - Campaign
  - Constituency Councils
  - Crime
  - Defense
  - Education
  - Energy/95th Congress
  - Environment
  - Federal Judge Selections
  - Foreign Relations
  - Foreign Relations/Panama Canal
  - General
  - Guest Workers
  - Hayakawa Involvement Program (Box 4)
  - Human Resources, 95th Congress
  - Interior
  - Internships
  - Kennedy, Edward M.
  - Labor
  - Legal cases
  - Legislative Agenda, 1982
  - Legislative Initiatives and Accomplishments
    - 1979
    - 95th-97th Congresses
  - Legislative Reports (Box 5)
    - Two Year, 1977-1978
    - Three Month
      - 1979
        - January-March
        - April-June
        - July-September
        - October-December
      - 1980
        - January-March
        - April-June
        - July-September
        - October-December
      - 1981
        - January-March
        - April-June
        - July-September
        - October-December
      - 1982
        - January-March
        - April-June
        - July-September
        - (for see Daily Legislative Reports and Congressional Record Fact Sheets), October-December 1982
    - Weekly (Box 6)
      - 1979
        - January-March
        - April-December
      - 1980
      - 1981-1982
  - Media/legislation
  - Memos to state offices
  - National Highway Traffic Safety Administration
  - 97th Congress/legislative procedure
  - Personnel (Box 7)
    - General
    - Compliments
    - Interns (Box 8-9)
    - Legislative Department Organization/job descriptions (Box 10)
    - Staff travel
  - Position papers/speeches, 1979
  - Pro/Con SIH letters
  - Reclamation
  - Recommendation letters (Box 11)
  - Regulatory Accomplishments
  - Relocation of Civilians
  - Republican Conference
  - Ruppert, Michael C.
  - School/student groups
  - SIH
  - Senate
  - Senate/House Selected Activities, 1982
  - Senatorial Campaign Committee
  - Senior Citizens
  - Small Business
  - Small Business/96th Congress
  - Staff Weekly Reports (Box 12)
    - 1982
      - January-May
      - June-December
  - State offices
  - Transportation
  - Daily Legislative Reports (Box 13)
    - 1979-1980
    - 1981-1982 (Box 14)
    - 1982 (Box 15)
  - S. 49 - Small Business Administration Review Court (Box 16)
  - S. 126 - Earthquake Hazards Reduction
  - S. 196 - Excise Tax; Aeronautics in Agriculture; Gasoline Tax
  - S. 274 - Prohibit Armed Forces Unionization
  - S. 297 - Imported Meat Tests
  - S. 373 - To Amend Maritime Mammal Protection Act (tuna fishing industry)
  - S. 503 - The Youth Employment Act of, 1977
  - S. 730 - Amend Internal Revenue Code Rate - reductions for individual taxes
  - S. 731 - Amend Internal Revenue Code - tax credit for creation of new jobs
  - S. 732 - Amend Internal Revenue Code - reduce tax for small business corps.
  - S. 733 - Amend Internal Revenue Code - increase amount of dividend exclusion
  - S. 734 - Amend Internal Revenue Code - exclusion from tax on limited savings
  - S. 735 - Amend Internal Revenue Code - permit depreciation of property
  - S. 736 - American Stock Ownership Plans for those of modest income
  - S. 737 - Amend Internal Revenue Code - Tax incentives for energy conservation
  - S. 961 - Amendment to opportunities for Adoption Act
  - S. 972 - Small Business Develpoment Center Act
  - S. 1010 - National Consumer Cooperative Bank Act
  - S. 1011 - Sex Crimes; Children; Pornography, photography, etc.
  - S. 1034 - Saccharin Bills
  - S. 1034 - Study effects of saccharin (Box 17)
  - S. 1040 - Child Exploitation Prevention Act
  - S. 1051 - Federal Grain Inspection
  - S. 1276 - To permit expended amount re pollution control facilities
  - S. 1303 - Amend legal services Corp Act
  - S. 1307 - Military Discharges; Veterans
  - S. 1328 - The Career Education Implementation Act of, 1977
  - S. 1358 - The San Luis Unit, Central Valley Project
  - S. 1361 - Academic Freedom Act
  - S. 1382 - Capital Punishment
  - S. 1495 - Construction of Bikeways
  - S. 1503 - Reimbursement of Tris
  - S. 1552 - To Amend the Marine Mammal Protection Act
  - S. 1585 - The Protection of Children from Sexual Exploitation Act of, 1977
  - S. 1614 - To Establish the Western States Conservation Program
  - S. 1632 - Amend Fed. Food, Drug & Cosmetic Act
  - S. 1644 - Tax deductions f/ heads of households
  - S. 1689 - Private bill for relief of Jenny Forbes
  - S. 1706
  - S. 1719 - Alien SSI payments attribution of sponsor's income
  - S. 1726 - Amend Small Business Act declare national policy
  - S. 1767 - Federal Officials Anti-defamation Act
  - S. 1780 - Improved administration of education
  - S. 1860 - Tax Relief Act
  - S. 1868 - A bill to expedite movement of Alaskan crude oil
  - S. 1872 - A bill to provide price support for sugar
  - S. 1894 - A bill for relief of California Canners and Growers
  - S. 1897 - Auth. grants of developing inst. to establish endowments
  - S. 1924 - Relief for Mark Charles Mieir & Liane Maira Mieir
  - S. 1950 - Foreign Surveillance Protection Act
  - S. 1967 - Social Security; Accounting; Social Security- States
  - S. 1974 - Regulatory Flexibility Act
  - S. 2020 - Longshoremen and Harbor Workers' Compensation
  - S. 2032 - Relief for Ionica Moldoveanu Nicolaica
  - S. 2036 - To promote amateur athletic activity in the U.S.
  - S. 2042 - Amend Rehabilitation Act of, 1973
  - S. 2107 - Amend Emergency Petro. Act of, 1973
  - S. 2142 - Internal Revenue Code, (1954)
  - S. 2169 - To name the South Portal Fed. Off. Bldg of HEW the Hubert Humphrey Bldg.
  - S. 2204 - Amend Sec. 4940 of IRS code reduce excise tax on invested income
  - S. 2218 - Establishing a national aquaculture policy, assessing status and establishing a strategy promotion of Aquaculture
  - S. 2304 - To require Hungarian relics remain in custody of U.S. Gov. unless Congress provides otherwise
  - S. 2305 - A Bill to Amend the Securities Act of, 1933
  - S. 2343 - A Bill to Ensure the Quality of Imported Meat
  - S. 2351 - To name the new VA Hospital in Little Rock after John McClelan
  - S. 2360 - Reimburse States for certain social service costs u/Social Security
  - S. 2369 - Dutch Elm Disease Control Act
  - S. 2385 - Agricultural Trade Expansion Act of, 1977
  - S. 2388 - Amend IRC - exclusion from gross income employer educational assistance programs
  - S. 2400 - National Alcohol Fuels Commission Act
  - S. 2405 - Intermediate Term Agricultural Export Credit Act
  - S. 2437 - Assistance for dam safety programs
  - S. 2462 - IRA Deductions for Individuals Already Participating in Retirement Plans
  - S. 2481 - Opportunities for Parity Pricing
  - S. 2483 - Directions to the Secretary of Agriculture re: exports
  - S. 2505 - Handicapped eligible for Social Security Assistance
  - S. 2534 - Health Maintenance Organizations Act Amendments
  - S. 2578 - To amend the Water Resources Planning Act
  - S. 2590 - Amend law relating to land claims in Riverside County, CA
  - S. 2627 - Deferred Compensation Plans
  - S. 2677 - For the Relief of Ching Wu Wang
  - S. 2685 - Youth Employment Incentive and Social Bonus Act, 1978
  - S. 2690 - Emergency Agricultural Assistance
  - S. 2711 - Revise and extend community education programs
  - S. 2727 - To promote and coordinate amateur athletic activity
  - S. 2738 - Tax Indexation Act
  - S. 2733 - To amend the Public Health Service Act - Rural Health
  - S. 2759 - Domestic Violence
  - S. 2778 - PCP criminal laws and procedures act
  - S. 2791 - Renegotiation Abeyance Act
  - S. 2843 - Gold Medallion Act
  - S. 2895 - Quotas on imported beef
  - S. 2990 - Implement International Sugar Agreement
  - S. 3007 - Tax treatment of individuals as employees
  - S. 3065 - Amend Internal Revenue Code to provide pre-1969 tax treatment for capital gains
  - S. 3093 - To provide for seizure, forfeiture, and disposition of vehicles used to illegally transport persons into US
  - S. 3111 - To amend the Internal Revenue Code of, 1954
  - S. 3138 - To amend the Internal Revenue Code of, 1954
  - S. 3147 - Taxation of fringe benefits
  - S. 3151 - Approp. for Department of Justice
  - S. 3205 - Amend the Indochina Migration and Refugee Assistance Act
  - S. 3217 - To exempt white water river running boats from requirements of Act requiring inspection and certification
  - S. 3245 - Boundary of Los Angeles National Forest
  - S. 3262 - Regulation of Federal Executive Departments
  - S. 3264 - Matching funds and assistance for states who reduce property taxes
  - S. 3285 - To amend the Internal Revenue Code of, 1954
  - S. 3288 - To amend the Internal Revenue Code of, 1954
  - S. 3300 - To amend Public Law 480
  - S. 3344 - For the relief of Rolf Erik Tibblin
  - S. 3350 - To maximize employment opportunities for all Americans...
  - S. 3360 - To amend the Urban Mass Transportation Act - increase minority opportunities in employment
  - S. 3414 - Amend IRC - non-resident aliens taxable gains on farming or undeveloped land at capital gains rates (Box 18)
  - S. 3422 - Establish Congressional Award program
  - S. 3471 - Fair Labor Standards Act
  - S. 3471 - Inflation Reduction and Job Protection Act
  - S. 3484 - Conveyance of certain public lands in San Bernardino County to the town of Red Mountain
  - S. 3530 - "Space Policy Act of ", 1978
  - S. 3527 - Funds for Robert A. Taft Institute of Government
  - H.R. 7769 - to authorize creation of a record of admission for permanent residence in the cases of refugees
  - S. 503 Amendment No. 39 - The Youth Employment Act of, 1977
  - Johnston Amendment No. 60
  - Packwood Amendment No. 62
  - Amendment No. 136 to H.R. 4876
  - Amendment No. 191 to the First Concurrent Budget Resolution FY, 1978
  - Amendment No. 247 To S. Con. Res. 19
  - No. 293 to S. 725 to extend certain programs of Ed. of the Handicapped Act
  - No. 300 to H.R. 5262 against any loans for the benefit of Vietnam, Laos, or Cambodia
  - Amendment No. 310 to S. 275 Barring food stamps for college students
  - Roth Amendment No. 340 Prohibiting sexual exploitation of children
  - Amendment No. 344 to S. 961 for a nationwide study of adoption codes
  - Amendment No. 365 to S. 252 to exempt grain elevators from dust emission control devices
  - Amendment No. 396 to S. 252 exempting grain elevators from air pollution control devices
  - Amendment No. 451 proposed to S. 957 The Consumer Controversies Resolution Act of, 1977
  - Amendment No. 452 proposed to S. 957 The Consumer Controversies Resolution Act of, 1977
  - Amendment No. 468 calling for no diplomatic relations with Cuba & no lifting of the trade embargo
  - Amendment No. 470 no fund made available to students in form of loans
  - Amendment No. 473 to H.R. 7555, barring use of funds to administer HEW affirmative action programs: hiring, promotions, admissions
  - Amendment No. 494 to S. 9 to delete section requiring mandatory disclosure of data interpretations
  - Amendment No. 698 to S. 926, supra.
  - Amendment No. 699 to S. 926, supra.
  - Amendment No. 700 to S. 926, supra.
  - Amendment No. 764 to increase funding for Agric. function from 5.6 bil. to 6.3 bil.
  - S. Res. 18, Amnesty Resolution (Allen)
  - S. Res. 38, President Ford Resolution
  - S. Res. 40, Amnesty Resolution (Allen)
  - S. Res. 76, Unilateral regulations by the European Economic Community
  - S. Res. 81, expulsion of George Krimsky by USSR
  - S.J. Res. 159, national water resources
  - S. Res. 168, The Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences, 50 Years
  - S. Res. 182, relations with Cuba; sense of Senate
  - S. Res. 219, establish a senior citizen intern program
  - S. Res. 225, to refer S. 1894 to Chief Commissioner of Claims
  - S. Res. 242, express Senate views on Ad. policy changes of IRS
  - S. Res. 271, establish a Commission of Domestic & International Hunger and Malnutrition
  - S. Res. 284, express Senate views on National Water Resources Man. Pol.
  - SR 302 to reorganize HUD
  - SR 311 that a moritorium be placed on grazing fee increases until opp. to hold hearing on proposal by Congress
  - SR 335 honoring W. C. Handy & proclaiming Memphis as the "Home of the Blues"
  - SR 336 proclaiming Memphis Slim as ambassador at large for goodwill
  - S. Res. 394, Commonwealth Club Commemoration
  - S. Res. 402, Antibiotics in animal feed
  - S. Res. 416, disapproving HEW standards relating to welfare provisions of SSA
  - S. Res. 442, commending Lee Williams for service to the Senate
  - S. Res. 457, congratulations to Taiwan on newly elected government
  - S. Res. 461, emigration visas for John and Lorraine Jodwalis
  - S. Res. 493, relative to the death of Rep. Ketchum of California
  - S. Res. 512, expressing the support of the Senate for the nomination for the 1978 Nobel Peace Prize
  - S. Res. 519, expressing the sense of the Senate with respect to selecting another site for the 1980 summer Olympics
  - S. R. 547, Rhodes Tavern preservation, District of Columbia
  - S. Res. 569, Direct Architect of Capitol to eliminate items in Hart SOB
  - S. Res. 593, Bartlett
  - S. Con. Res. 5, missing in action in Vietnam
  - S. Con. Res. 26, declaring war against amytrophic lateral schlerosis
  - S. Con. Res. 37, auto safety standards Congressional oversight
  - S. Con. Res. 38, to disapprove of the President's action:, 5/4/77
  - S C R Res. 41 to promote effective treatment of epilepsy
  - S. Con. Res. 45, support U.S. Olympic city nomination before International Committee
  - S. Con. Res. 65, resolution of federally-owned roadless areas
  - S. Con. Res. 68, expressing sense of the Senate on Baltic States question
  - S. Con. Res. 69, endorsing Rhodesian settlement
  - S. Con. Res. 73, import fees on crude oil
  - S. Con. Res. 79, disapproving proposed regulations regarding Firearms
  - S. Con. Res. 85, dismissal of indictments against FBI agents
  - S. Con. Res. 91, Cuban military intervention in Africa
  - S. Con, Res. 95, condemning the trials of Anatoly Shcharansky, Viktoras Petkus, and Aleksandr I. Ginzburg
  - S. Con. Res. 109, separation of powers between legislative and executive branch in termination of treaties
  - S.J. Res. 28, to limit the members of both Houses to 12 years service (Box 19)
  - S.J.R. 93, relating to the excess land provisions & residency requirements of the federal reclamation laws
  - S.J.R. 96, to postpone the effective date of final regulations relating to Fed. reclamation law until 12/31/78
  - S.J.R. 110 - "Sun Day"
  - S.J.R. 129, Halt construction of the Phillip A. Hart Building
  - S.J.R. 135, designating weekend of or preceding April 29, 1979, as "Days of Remembrance of Victims of the Holocaust"
  - S.J.R. 147, designating July 18, 1979, "POW-MIA Recognition Day"
  - S.J.R. 159, procedures for Congressional disapproval of national water resources policies
  - Printed amendments
  - Unprinted amendments
  - S. 2 - "Sunset Act of ", 1979
  - S. 12 - Cost of living adjustments
  - S. 29 - Davis Bacon Act repeal
  - S. 33 - To provide for permanent tax rate reductions for individuals
  - S. 34 - "Spending Limitation Act of ", 1979
  - S. 43 - To promote safety and health in skiing and other winter activities
  - S. 46 - Extending diplomatic privileges and immunities to officials representing the People's Republic of China in U.S.
  - S. 100 - Internal Revenue Code of amend to provide deduction for expenses - reforestation, 1954
  - S. 102 - Postpone increase in minimum wage and adjustment to tip credit under the Fair Labor Standards Act
  - S. 103 - "Save Our Schools Act"
  - S. 104 - Establish a uniform procedure for congressional review of agency rules
  - S. 105 - To prohibit and remedy the interstate restraint of children in violation of custody and visitation
  - S. 106 - Amend Social Security Act to provide for attributions of sponsor's income and resources to aliens for a period of 3 years
  - S. 110 - To amend Internal Revenue Code for small business
  - S. 114 - Death penalty
  - S. 117 - Raoul Wallenberg
  - S. 143 - Preservation of historic places in Washington, D.C.
  - S. 159 - Disapproving Pres. action re fee on oil imports, etc.
  - S. 176 - National Port Week
  - S. 186 - 200th Anniversary of American victory at Yorktown, VA
  - S. 192 - National Ministers Day
  - S. 195 - Medicare-Medicaid in teaching hospitals
  - S. 202 - Italian-American Heritage Week
  - S. 208 - To amend the Internal Revenue Code of - foreign visitors, 1954
  - S. 211 - Indexation of Individual Income Tax Brackets
  - S. 212 - Declaration of Policy
  - S. 219 - Amend Internal Revenue Code of, 1954
  - S. 221 - Congressional Award Program Act
  - S. 223 - International Trade Laws
  - S. 224 - Act to Prohibit Issuance of Regulation on Taxation of Fringe Benefits
  - S. 244 - To establish national space policy and program direction
  - S. 265 - Equal access to Justice Act
  - S. 323 - Repeal of National Speed Limit of 55 Miles Per Hour
  - S. 326 - "Taxpayers' Bill of Rights Act"
  - S. 336 - To amend IRC
  - S. 343 - International School of Islamabad
  - S. 386 - Family Farm Liberation Act
  - S. 388 - Small Business Employee Ownership Act
  - S. 399 - Federal Crop Insurance Act of, 1979
  - S. 401 - Model Adoption Legislation, disapproving certain aspects
  - S. 412 - Rescue attempt for American hostages in Iran
  - S. 414 - Federal patent procedure for Small Business and Non-profit Organizations
  - S. 432 - Taxing Social Security benefits
  - S. 449 - Charitable Organizations Preservation Act
  - S. 460 - Energy Efficient Cooling
  - S. 538 - U.S. trade practices
  - S. 576 - Private bill for Larry Grathwohl
  - S. 577 - Private bill for Jenny Flores
  - S. 587 - Food Additive Safety Amends.
  - S. 589 - Tax deductions for certain Mexico and Canada conventions
  - S. 598 - Soft drink bottlers permitted rights
  - S. 603 - More Medicaid services for severely disabled
  - S. 604 - Small Business Act amend.
  - S. 631 - Gold Medal for John Wayne
  - S. 633 - Possible Revision of the Reclamation Act of, 1902
  - S. 642 - Reduced mail rates for U.S. Olympic Committee
  - S. 710 - Interstate trucking (Box 20)
  - S. 791 - Angeles National Forest
  - S. 813 - Designate certain land in Shasta National Forest
  - S. 816 - Social Security and aliens receiving benefits
  - S. 818 - Prohibit banning of use of nitrites
  - S. 873 - IRC - Residency requirements for living abroad
  - S. 887 - Redbank and Fancher Creeks, CA
  - S. 955 - Taxpayers Bill of Rights Act
  - S. 982 - Amend Food Stamp Act
  - S. 1052 - Bi-lingual ballots
  - S. 1070 - 3 year residency requirement for aliens
  - S. 1107 - 85% of minimum wage for 16-20 year olds
  - S. 1121 - Saccharin
  - S. 1158 - Amend the Clean Air Act Amendments
  - S. 1163 - Carryover Basis Provisions
  - S. 1173 - Time-Sensitive Business Communications
  - S. 1176 - Limit Pres. in Designation of National Monuments under Antiqu. Act
  - S. 1198 - SOHIO
  - S. 1287 - Repeal earnings ceiling for Soc. Sec. Act
  - S. 1200 - Alcohol Fuels Regulatory Simplification Act
  - S. 1301 - A bill to amend the Longshoremen's and Harbor Workers' Compensation Act
  - S. 1330 - Omnibus Geothermal Energy Development Act of, 1979
  - S. 1357 - Reimburse CA for Work on Suisun Marsh
  - S. 1361 - Feasibility Study for Shasta Dam
  - S. 1382 - Soc. Sec. & AFDC Program
  - S. 1400 - Trucking Competition & Safety Act
  - S. 1427 - U.S. Mexican Good Neighbor Act of, 1979
  - S. 1435 - Capital recovery for investment in plant and equipment
  - S. 1465 - Farm Credit Act Amendments
  - S. 1481 - Creation of Small Business Participating Debenture
  - S. 1486 - Exemptions from the Occupat. Safety/Health Act of, 1970
  - S. 1572 - Family farms and OSHA
  - S. 1597 - Economic stimulation of economy
  - S. 1598 - Social Security coverage of state and local employees
  - S. 1615 - Relief of James Thronwell
  - S. 1619 - Tax credits
  - S. 1645 - Credit for interest received on savings
  - S. 1647 - JACL
  - S. 1650 - Aquaculture
  - S. 1660 - Civil Defense Program
  - S. 1680 - Western Lands Distribution and Reclamation Equalization
  - S. 1711 - Santa Ana River Flood Control Project
  - S. 1735 - Congressional Pay Cap
  - S. 1741 - Preservation of American Antiquities
  - S. 1775 - Dev. Energy from Ag. Commodities
  - S. 1792 - Strike Gold Medal for Simon Wiesenthal
  - S. 1860 - Small Business Innovation
  - S. 1862 - Federal Firearms Laws
  - S. 1866 - Indochina Migration & Refugee Assistance Act of, 1975
  - S. 1913 - Wine Taxation
  - S. 1914 - Urban Mass Transport
  - S. 1964 - Rollover accounts
  - S. 2007 - RARE II
  - S. 2027 - Relief of James Daniel Bronson
  - S. 2077 - California Pacific Fishery Management Council
  - S. 2104 - Increase export opportunities for small businesses
  - S. 2149 - Amend Ag. Adjustment Act
  - S. 2153 - OSH Improvements Act
  - S. 2179 - Definition of artificial bait
  - S. 2216 - Improve the intelligence system of the U.S.